(Penny:)Still mad at me about that?
(Leonard:)No. No, I understand.
(Leonard:)I got too intense,
you had to back off.
(Bernadette:)Thank you.
(Leonard:)I've gotten a lot better
at that, you know.
(Leonard:)I've dated four different women
since we broke up
(Leonard:)and I didn't tell any of them
that I loved them
(Leonard:)and wanted
to have their babies.
(Bernadette:)Good for you.
(Leonard:)Okay, good night.
(Leonard:)Good night.
(Penny:)You know, maybe it wouldn't be
the worst idea in the world
(Penny:)to violate the Neutral Zone
for just one night.
(Howard:)Oh!
(Raj:)Hey, Leonard,
Sheldon kicked me
(Raj:)out of the room,
gave me your key.
(Leonard:)Penny's here.
(Leonard:)No, we don't want to watch
Bridget Jones's Diary!